Hello everyone, welcome to you investors.
Today we will see which companies have
hosted their quarterly results
and how have their results been. So let's
start. First of all, let's go to the
numbers of Himadri Special Tea. The last
trading price was Rs 144. Its
market cap is Rs 6341 crore.
We are seeing more honey in sales and percentage
growth. But
if we talk about net profit, then a profit of 123% is
seen.
Specially in the chemical business,
this company works completely. You can keep this company in your account.
See, whenever we
overview the numbers of any company,
you should know that we only
overview those companies which are
giving a decent performance in the stock market. All
you have to do is keep that
company in your eye. And if
you feel that the company is giving a very good
performance, then you
can also consider investing in it. After doing
your due, the next company is
ICC Lombard is a large-cap company,
and we're seeing a 14% increase in sales and a
12% increase in net profit. It's a general
insurance company. As the population in the country continues to
grow, the demand for insurance will
also continue to grow. You
can take your own decision later. The next company
belongs to the IT sector. Its name is
L&T Technology. It's a large-cap
company. With a last trading price of ₹4,068,
we're seeing a 15% increase in sales
and a 13% increase in net profit.
As long as India continues to
grow, the IT sector will continue to
grow. This is the era of IT and
technology.
India is also trying its hand in space, so there will
always be demand for these companies in the market.
You can plan your investment in this company and many other IT companies like it. The
numbers we're
looking at next are for Indus Land Bank.
This is a large-cap company with sales.
We are seeing a growth of 31%
and at the same time, we are seeing a growth of 32% in net profit. These are
very good numbers.
Now we will have to see tomorrow
how the market welcomes the numbers of this company. The
numbers look quite impressive to me. The
next company is ICC Prudential
Life Insurance. This
company works in the business of life insurance. Again, this is a large
cap type company. The last trading
price was ₹575. We are seeing a
growth of 1552% in sales
and ₹30% in net profit. The next company is
Poly Cab India.
This company works in the wiring cable business. We are seeing a
growth of 42% in sales and 82% in net profit.
We are seeing some very impressive numbers. This is a
very good result. I definitely give
it a thumbs up. Now as the
banks start reducing their interest rates,
we will see a boom in the real estate sector as well.
Consequently, the
numbers of Poly Cab will also increase.  We'll see even greater improvement,
because
whenever banks raise interest rates,
people often either make their home purchase plans postpaid
or drop them. Now,
as banks begin lowering interest rates,
we'll see even more growth in this company. You
can consider investing in this company by investing in your debit card. The
next company is Mishthan
Foods. I've selected this company because it belongs to the
small-cap category,
but its numbers,
both quarter-on-quarter and quarter-on-quarter,
look impressive to me. You
can see on your screen how
we're seeing a 500% growth rate in profit. The
company is quite small, so
before investing in such a company,
you need to consider the
areas in which the company is operating, the
status of its operations, and where
it exports. If so, the
next company for which we're
seeing impressive numbers is
Sheetal, basically ice cream.  The company works in a business of Rs
41 crore with a market cap. It is a
very small company. The stock can crash by 82.90% at any time.
If any bad news comes, then
you can add this company to your list
and keep it in mind while tracking its growth.
This is some
kind of investment opportunity for you. The next company
is Ganesh Housing.
This is also a small cap type company. We are seeing a growth of 536% in sales
and 1100% growth in net profit.
Now watch it
on YouTube. I
cannot advise any investor to make any kind of investment in this company
because if
any person who is not authorized by SEBI to
promote any financial instrument does so, then he is
fined
and can also be barred from the stock market.
So the bottom line is that you should
study the numbers of the companies I have just shown you on your own. And if
you have any query, then please
post it in the comment section. So that's all for now.  If
you found it informative, then
like and share the video and
subscribe to the channel so that the
notifications of all the upcoming important videos can
reach you first. With this we will meet in the
next video.